Guide to the Mabel Loomis Todd Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Financial Records, 1882-1948; Series VIII; 3.25 linear feet (9 boxes)
  - Correspondence
    - Securities Co., 1928 (Box 124, Folder 72)
    - Southern Pacific Co., 1912 (Box 124, Folder 73)
    - Spencer, Claise S., 1930 (Box 124, Folder 73)
    - Staples, F.M., 1910 (Box 124, Folder 73)
    - Stewart, W.J., 1925-1926 (Box 124, Folder 73)
    - Street's Western Stable Car Line, 1915 (Box 124, Folder 73)
    - Suffolk Savings Bank, 1934 (Box 124, Folder 73)
    - Sunshine Fruit Co., 1918, 1924, 1927 (Box 124, Folder 73)
    - Thomas, Irving J., 1918-1931 (Box 124, Folder 74)
    - Travelers Insurance Co., 1925 (Box 124, Folder 75)
    - United States Government, Steamboat Inspection Service, 1922, 1927 (Box 124, Folder 75)
    - United States Treasury, Internal Revenue Service, 1914, 1921 (Box 124, Folder 75)
    - United States Trust Co. of New York, 1927, 1932 (Box 124, Folder 75)
    - University Club, 1913 (Box 124, Folder 75)
    - Vindicator Consolidated Gold Mining Co., 1906 (Box 124, Folder 75)
    - Western Alkali Co., 1906-1907 (Box 124, Folder 75)
    - Wilder, Herbert Augustus: will, 1923 (Box 124, Folder 75)
    - William (B.H. & Co.), 1913 (Box 124, Folder 75)
    - Williams, McCloud & Co., 1925 (Box 124, Folder 76)
    - Winchester Savings Bank, 1934 (Box 124, Folder 76)
    - Wood, William H., 1922 (Box 124, Folder 76)
    - Unidentified, 1924, undated (Box 124, Folder 76)
  - Miscellaneous Records
    - Financial notes, 1863-1935, undated (Box 124, Folder 77-78)
    - Records books
      - "Board and expenses, Robert Baker", 1904-1922, undated (Box 124, Folder 79)
      - "Camp Aloha, Money Expended", 1907-1908 (Box 124, Folder 80)
      - "Long distance telephone calls" and "Kilbornes", 1911, undated (Box 124, Folder 81)
    - Record of Mabel Loomis Todd's expenses and her trip to Europe, 1886 (Box 124, Folder 82)
    - Deeds, 1921, 1926 (Box 124, Folder 83)
    - Federal income tax returns, 1913, 1916, 1918 (Box 124, Folder 84)
    - Mabel Loomis Todd's early will [AMS], 1881 (Box 124, Folder 85)
    - Wills of Mabel Loomis Todd, 1916, 1919, 1922-1934 (Box 124, Folder 86-87)
  - Property
    - Observatory House, Amherst, Massachusetts: lists of furnishings, receipts for repairs and correspondence, 1898-1920 (Box 125, Folder 88)
    - Orchard Street House, Amherst, Massachusetts: plans and correspondence, 1917-1925 (Box 125, Folder 89)
    - House at Fairhaven, Massachusetts: list of items moved to Hog Island, Maine, 1909 (Box 125, Folder 90)
    - Triangle Park, Amherst, Massachusetts: receipts and correspondence, 1903-1912 (Box 125, Folder 91)
      See also: box 16, folder 410.
    - Coconut Grove house: legal documents, 1925 (Box 125, Folder 91)
    - Matsuba
      - Mabel Loomis Todd's suggestions for a house: correspondence, 1918-1922 (Box 125, Folder 92)
      - Correspondence
        - 1932-1935 (Box 125, Folder 93)
        - 1936 January-March (Box 125, Folder 94)
        - 1936 April (Box 125, Folder 95)
        - 1936 May (Box 125, Folder 96)
        - 1936 September-November (Box 125, Folder 97)
        - 1937 March-April (Box 125, Folder 97)
        - 1944, 1946 February-December (Box 125, Folder 98)
        - 1947 January-June (Box 125, Folder 99)
        - 1948 Jan, undated (Box 125, Folder 99)
      - Inventory of household items
        - 1933 (Box 125, Folder 100)
        - 1935 (Box 125, Folder 101)
      - Financial notes and tax receipts, 1932, 1935-1936, undated (Box 125, Folder 102)
      - Legal documents, 1936 (Box 125, Folder 103-104)
      - Leases, 1941-1946 (Box 125, Folder 105)